The Knights on
offense now.
My God!
He just sent
the defense flying!
That man just was
thrown two
feet in the air.
That is unreal.
They
look unstoppable.
Whoo!
You like that?
Hey, hey!
Time out!
What the hell is
going on with him, man?
The intensity just
went through
the roof.
I think I know
what's going on.
Hey!
Ref!
I want to file
a complaint.
These guys
are using steroids and
I want to file an immediate investigation.
Oh, come on, Ted!
You can't just
accuse me of cheating
with steroids
because I'm winning.
What kind
of slander is that?
You call
that slander?
Look around, idiot!
Everyone's drained,
and your guys
are turning into
monsters, alright?
Don't play
stupid with me.
So what if I did?
I have every official
in my back pocket.
Go, go, go.
Check for yourself.
You'll find nothing.
You really think
games like this
are won
on the field?
Please!
Every game
like this is run
by the rich
behind the scenes.
You broke losers
never even
had a chance.
Smart girl.
Give me a kiss.
You see, Ted, you can
break your back
your whole life
trying to
start a family,
but Emma
does not care.
I can treat her
however I want,
and she'll
never leave me.
I have money.
She's trash.
And I couldn't care
less about her.
But this game?
I will win.